Hello everyone, first of all, thank you for the invitation, I am very honored to be able to share some of my 3D experience with you on behalf of my company.
First of all, I have worked in this industry for more than 20 years.
Then in 2018, I started my 3D journey in my first year of military service.
At that time, we often talk about what is the trend of fashion in the clothing industry.
But at that time, I found that 3D fashion is our future trend.
In the past 7 years of my 3D fashion experience, I have worked with different fashion brands, and with different companies.
According to the customer's different needs, we provide different 3D output.
For example, when we work with some brands, we usually provide some 3D CPOJ to the customer.
Then the customer follows our requirements to see our products.
For example, some customers who do not have 3D software yet, we provide some front and rear cars,
and some pictures to them to see the fashion.
Through different pictures, there are virtual images, and some pictures of different pressure marks.
Then we show them the fashion results, and we cooperate with them.
Then there are some other things, we can do some different fashion accessories.
For example, we can do some different fashion accessories.
Later, I will share them with you.
I will share 4 different things with you.
First of all, the customer's fashion.
Next page.
Then, in general, in our industry,
no matter what kind of project or product it is,
we can divide the fashion into the stage of product development and production.
Then, according to our different stages, we can apply it to our 3D area.
For example, in the past, in traditional fashion,
we may start from scratch,
according to the requirements of different customers,
the support of the fabric, and the style,
and then slowly get the fabric out,
and then produce, cut, and assemble,
and then do some fitting tests.
It may take about 14 working days.
But the result may not necessarily be good.
Maybe after we see it,
it will be wasted in vain.
14 working days.
But we can, through our 3D,
maybe in about 7 days,
maybe faster,
we can apply it to our fast-moving board,
and at the same time,
produce a virtual sample.
This is not only for us to improve sales,
but also for the customer to have a
seamless connection.
Then, in 3D,
we can select and modify the model.
In addition to saving costs,
we can also save time.
Then, as I just said,
we can use different 3D samples,
for example, some pressure maps,
and transparency maps,
to see the results.
Then, we can directly share the models
with the customers on a platform,
and then let the customers
inspect our samples.
Then, we can continue to the next step.
Then, in this development and production process,
we can...
In the past,
we were constantly working on the samples,
and then,
we can go to the market.
But now,
we have applied this 3D process,
we can directly display the 3D samples,
and then,
we can inspect them.
Then, we can probably do one or two samples,
and then,
we can launch the market.
Next page.
So,
in terms of the sample type,
we can divide it into two categories.
First,
we can use the sample type
to display different samples.
We have different types of samples.
Generally speaking,
in the sample section,
we can divide it into two types.
The first type is
to look at the design of the sample.
Then,
in each sample time,
14 days for the sample,
plus 7 days for the customer's sample.
It's about 21 days.
Then,
for example,
it may have to be the second round.
Then, after the second round,
we can take the sample.
We may call it the sales section.
After the sales section,
we can...
The customers may also ask us
to take a sample.
The sales section.
After the sample,
we can have the customer
to check the sample,
to test the sample.
Then,
before the product is produced,
we have a mass production section.
So,
there are different types of samples.
But,
if we put this thing
in our 3D,
In 3D, we can reduce a lot of unnecessary boards.
For example, we can apply it to sales boards and some magnetic boards.
We can use 3D to build boards, and then we can use virtual SMS to apply it to SMS.
We can also use SMS to see if there are any bad things in different telemachines.
We can see if there are any regulations for bad telemachines.
On the right side, we have some products from our company.
All of them are built like this.
Whether it's underwear or sports underwear,
we can put them on different boards.
This way, customers can apply our 3D products at different stages.
For example, we are in the middle of the season.
Traditionally, we may need 168 days to build our different boards and then produce them.
But for example, if we apply it to 3D, we may only have about 90 days.
That's it.
Thank you.
Next slide, please.
02 is the digital production network that we talked about.
As I said, we have different stages through 3D.
Then, through our 3D tools, we can apply our different 3D needs in different scenarios.
For example, we can roughly divide what we call normal 3D.
In this 3D model, there're multiple models capabilities.
We can apply products you've have come with.
They can hit the 3D so that when the product passes to our 3D editor,
the 3D laptop will use the 3D training system with the 3D machine,
or can respond through the purchase and acceptance system.
The public can turn the product to 3D,
and they will allow a pattern incomparably.
… i'll move to other results THAT i can't even contain myself.
It's only in theaza that we can let the product pass.
For example, we can use it in different sales environments, for example, in a shop, virtual showroom, or in animation, or in different scenarios.
Next page.
This is the only example. You can see that there are about 10 styles.
In fact, from the beginning, we only have one style.
From this one style, we can separate it into 10 styles of different styles.
We can add different fabrics, different styles of transparency.
Then, from these 10 styles, we can add different styles and create more than 100 styles.
So, in 3D printing, this can greatly improve our efficiency.
Next page.
As I just said, for example, now we have one style,
we can add different prints and different effects.
Also, how to change from a simple one to a more sporty style.
Then, these are all the styles that some of our customers have used before.
From a simple style, we can add fabric, print, and logo, and create different styles.
Next page.
In general, in addition to the closet platform, we can view the styles.
We can also add a front and back car, and a front and back car to show the customers the style.
In general, we can also provide a selection map for customers to see.
Then, they can quickly see the style's effect.
Then, what are the changes?
We can also provide some transparent and pressure maps.
Then, it's easy to understand what styles need to be changed.
Thank you.
Next page.
Then, there are all the necessary color versions.
In the closet platform, we have a very simple colorway.
We can add different colorways.
We can replace some of the traditional colorways that we used to have.
Then, there are different versions.
The first is to waste time.
The second is to waste unnecessary materials.
Then, it's faster to show the customer.
Next page.
Then you can go to the Cloud Closet platform.
This platform can be used as a database.
Then we share our 3D data with our customers through this database.
Then the customers follow their different requirements.
In general, our customers will provide VQS,
which is the requirements for virtual quality.
We improve the communication method according to this requirement.
Then we quickly approve a payment.
As I said, we only have normal 3D.
Then,
why do we call these 3D sales?
Because in addition to the 3D we usually make,
we can also add different 3D effects.
For example, we can put some more authentic 3D brochures
on the cloud platform.
Then, according to different requirements,
we can put this document
in a picture time
and place it on a table for some photos.
Next page.
Then, we can put some more AI in addition to the 3D design we just talked about.
We can also put some internal structure pictures.
Then, we can add more images.
Then, we can see if we can make some animations.
Then, we can see from our animation
that our product has a very breathable effect.
Of course, for example,
these things can't be done with just one source.
Next page.
In addition to those structural images,
we can also make some display images.
For example, this example is the same.
How do we go from a person's platform,
a virtual platform,
to a model,
and then roll it around
to display different colors?
Then, there are some other things.
For example,
we call it virtual showroom.
Virtual showroom.
Let me give you an example.
For example,
in the past, we used a traditional model.
We finished making a set of products.
Then, we have to put it in a scene to take pictures.
It takes a lot of time.
It may take two to three months.
But if we use this 3D model,
for example,
the one on the right,
as an example,
we can finish it in about two to three weeks.
Then, for example,
there are some customers who can directly choose a product here.
It seems that we can add some AR products here.
You can choose a product here at a glance.
You can place an order.
Then, is it going to be successful?
Yes, it is going to be successful.
I think it's going to be successful.
So, there are many other examples,
you can put a product here,
and then you will have a look at it.
Personally,
I think this is one of the most important reasons
to analyze what we're doing and what we're doing now.
The first point,
we don't have an idea of what to do.
There are many different ways to analyze it.
This is to say,
we need to analyze,
analyze,
analyze.
So, it can be a lot of things.
So, the first point is that
you can think about the material in this.
The second point is that
if you have a 3D model,
to do a scan, and then it seems that in the fabric, we can roughly divide the texture and the properties of the fabric.
Through some products, we can get the texture and properties we need more accurately.
And then, of course, before we say we have finished, we need to understand that different countries
have different patterns and requirements for fitting.
For example, on the right side of the picture, we can see that there is a fatter one and a thinner one.
We can understand it easily.
And then, we can use different requirements to make different fabrics for different customers.
And then, there is a very big difference.
Of course, in addition to 3D, one of the biggest issues is that we need to use 3D to apply the fabric.
So, for example, just now, we have a pattern.
We put it here.
We use the fabric to make a pattern.
And then, we can change it to make it easier for customers to see.
And then, on the right side of the example,
if you don't know how to use the fabric,
you may have to stitch it.
And then, there will be some stitches on the bottom.
There will be some stitches.
So, we must be familiar with the requirements of the fabric
so that we can apply the fabric in 3D.
And then, we can get a better result.
Next slide, please.
Of course, in addition to what I said just now,
the last point is that for a 3D designer,
personal participation and coordination skills are, of course, a very good point.
That is to say, we can apply our 3D to different things.
For example,
the one on the left is a seamless thing.
In addition to what we usually use for sewing products,
we can also apply this 3D to some seamless,
integrated styles.
And then, for example, the one on the right,
how can we apply it to different styles in the lower body?
And then, we can apply it to our 3D.
For example, we can apply it to our 3D app,
to some sales points,
and also to some virtual events.
We can apply it to all of these aspects.
Let's come to the conclusion.
In the clothing industry,
in fact, in the past,
our traditional scale of cross-production,
now,
we have a small unit.
For example,
many of our old brand items,
we may have,
from the past,
we have now,
many of them,
are more flexible in the production model.
In the industry,
we have reduced costs,
and then,
quick replacement,
there is demand.
And then,
through the industry,
our current requirements,
such as the production unit,
sales,
increase efficiency,
and then,
increase the cost of production.
And then,
we can make our
in this clothing,
the demand of digital products,
this school can
export some new talents,
this is a good place.
And then,
we hope that the school can cooperate,
together,
to create a cross-digital,
digital integration ecosystem,
for some students,
to be able to connect to our
bubble line in the industry.
And finally,
I just simply say that,
there are a few points,
that is,
we can,
now,
we just have to
cut short
the distance between
integration and the industry.
That is,
our future students can
come out of our school,
and then,
very soon,
they can compete with
our entire industry.
And then,
we can
quickly improve,
that is,
their rapid application
of digitalization
in our industry.
And then,
the innovation of the industry,
and then,
the training,
they have 3D design,
and then,
3D real-time layout.
And then,
to add,
how to do a 3D sales,
and then,
we can improve our future
opportunities,
to,
to, to,
Thank you, everyone.
As you can see, this is a relatively simple T-tie bracelet.
We can add different effects to show you on a foreign TV.
There are also different people, not just one person.
We can also show you some thinner and fatter ones.
Thank you.